

# TAKATA KEI

Full stack & Blockchain Engineer

- ☑ goldone0101@gmail.com
- Tokyo, Japan

- in linkedin.com/in/takata-kei-023292242
- https://t.me/goldoneen
- github.com/goldoneen
- goldoneen.github.io

#### SUMMARY

Experienced full stack developer with a strong background in developing awardwinning applications for a diverse clientele. 7+ years of industry experience includes programming, debugging, and wireframes. Also, I handle tasks with accuracy and efficiency. I love to write code in a high-paced and challenging environment with an emphasis on using best practices to develop high quality software that meets project requirements, budget, and schedule. As a developer, enjoy learning new technologies and sharing findings with my colleagues.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Blockchain full stack Engineer**

Nov 2021 - Feb 2022

 Built sophisticated smart contracts like staking marketplace offers, troubleshot production issues, contributed to gas fee optimization, and deployed into Ethereum mainnet.

- · Migrated smart contracts from Ethereum to Polygon and existing assets (NFTs, offers, collections) to newly deployed contracts on Polygon.
- Performed a Web3 integration with the smart contracts on Next.js.
- Built subgraph endpoints to interact with the smart contract triggered events and deploy them into the graph protocol.
- Worked closely with other protocols like Rarible, Aave, and Compound.

#### **Technologies:**

Solidity Ethereum Polygon Web3.js Subgraph Solana DeFi





**Digitalax** 

## Looksrare

## **Blockchain Full-stack Engineer**

Feb 2021 - Oct 2021

- · Built a front-end application for minting and staking NFTs using React and
- Contributed to a contract for NFT registration and redemption with Solidity.
- · Created a POC Vue.js front-end platform for an NFT gallery using Moralis and
- Worked on the token distribution and migration from BSC to Polygon network using BscScan, PolygonScan API, and Solidity.

#### **Technologies:**

Blockchain Solidity Web3.js Ether.js Moralis React Vue.js JavaScript



#### **Blockchain Full-stack Engineer**

**Gelato Network** 

May 2020 - Jan 2021

- Developed automated trading strategies on Uniswap and QuickSwap.
- · Built smart contract with solidity and deployed using Truffle.
- Used Flashbots API to fetch block info regarding trading pool and staking.
- · Worked on building trading view, swap modal using React, Next, TypeScript, Web3.js, and Subgraph.
- Supported limit orders on the Ethereum Mainnet and Polygon (Matic).

# **Technologies:**

Ethereum Ploygon Solidity Oracle React Next Node.js

TypeScript









#### **Full-Stack Developer**

Cave Consulting Group

Jan 2019 - Mar 2020

- Developed an Angular, RxJS, and Angular Material web app for managing user registration for seminars and webinars hosting in Firebase.
- Built out the frontend and created a Node.js back end with Firebase cloud function and Firestore as the database while Google Storage was used as file storage
- Took 100% responsibility for the project of planning, architecture, development, and deployment.

## **Technologies:**

Angular Firebase Node.js JavaScript React Vue Next Material-UI Bootstrap Google API

## Front end Developer

Holidu

Techno Pro

Mar 2018 - Sep 2018

- Integrated Redux and MobX on a number of React-based front-end projects for the better state management of React components.
- Implemented a GraphQL-and-Apollo server for a React-and-Vue.js front-end data query.
- Created a new customized chart library using D3.js and Plotly.js.
- Embedded a Google tag manager and Google Analytics for the website conversion tracking and the user event tracking.

## **Technologies:**

GraphQL React Next Vue.js TypeScript Material UI

#### **Full-Stack Developer**

May 2015 - Dec 2017

- Worked as intern developer on Web and mobile application developments.
- Built out several websites with PHP, Node.js and Javascript frameworks.

#### **Technologies:**

jQuery JavaScript WordPress Node.js Vue.js

# **SKILLS & TOOLS**

#### Web

HTML/CSS/SCSS

JavaScript/Typescript

React/Vue/Angular

Next/Nuxt/Gatsby WordPress/Shopify

Node.js/ASP.NET

Python/Ruby/PHP

PostgreSQL/MySQL/MongoDB

AWS/GCP/Azure

#### **Blockchain**

Web3.js/Ether.js

Solidity/Rust Hardhat/Truffle

Infura/Moralis Eth/BSC/Polygon/Avalanche/Solana

## **PROFESSIONAL**

**Effective communication** 

**Team player** 

Strong problem solver Good time management

Fast learner

#### **EDUCATION**

### The University of Tokyo

Bachelor's degree Computer Science 2011 - 2015

## **LANGUAGE**

**English** 

## **INTERESTS**

Climbing Swimming

Travelling

Photography

# **MY PROJECTS**

https://app.highlord.io

https://www.climbtoken.finance https://home.babyswap.finance

https://app.eurxb.finance

https://www.powned.co

https://fractional.art

https://www.mdhearingaid.com https://www.smartbuycars.us

https://www.bloopersstore.in